This video gives a brief introduction to the Arclight's device.
Once attached to the side hole of the direct ophthalmoscope will be placed directly
over the center of the lens that your mobile camera uses in the video
mode.
The camera will function just like your eyes.
When you are looking through the side hole, to confirm which lens to
line up the side hole with, open the video up on your phone.
Place your finger over each lens in turn.
When the screen goes dark, you have covered the lens used for video.
Remove the yellow paper from the back of the clip.
Place the points of the arrow over the center of the lens used to capture video.
Press the clip down firmly.
Remove the arrow.
The clip should now be in the correct position.
To video the reflex switch on the director of Talmosco, end of the act
lights and select
the brightest light with three clicks.
Make sure the lens rack is at the top.
With the light facing away from the phone towards the patient, place the act light in
the clip and pull the elastic over to secure.
Push the act lights up until it cannot slide any further.
The slide hole of the director of the oscilloscope will now be directly over
the center of the
lens that's capture video.
To record the external eye, use the other end of the device.
To capture image now, open the video up and zoom in filling the screen
with the view
through the side hole.
Press record and perform the examination.
Press stop and save the video.
You can now share with colleagues on SQR encrypted platforms only for the purpose you gained
conceptified from the patients.
Enjoy using the act lights in my job.